Sally Hedges

Tel: 01472 852978 Mob: 07900571877 Email: sallyhedges77@gmail.co.uk GitHub: https://github.com/Sally077

PROFILE

Computer Science teacher that has worked in Education for over 20 years working with a diverse range of educational settings as an ICT Teacher. My job role has evolved, and I have worked as a Computer Science teacher teaching Python for over 5 years. I enrolled in a front-end developer bootcamp in December 2022 and have immersed myself in learning HTML, CSS, JavaScript. In addition to these programs, I have also become familiar with bootstrap, using third party APIs and have practiced the basics of TDD and began to work in React.

I would like to improve my knowledge and understanding of Programming. I enjoy programming in Python and have enrolled on a frontend developer bootcamp in December 2022. Since my time in the bootcamp I have engaged in the bootcamp program and have put in over 30 hours a week as well as currently working full time as a teacher. I have also completed group projects in the course and have been nominated team leader in an API development project.

CORE SKILLS

HTML	CSS	JavaScript
jQuery	TDD	API development
Node	Boot Strap	

KEY ACHIEVEMENTS

- 2023 Ed X Front End Developer Boot Camp
- 2022 Attended a Higher Attainment in Computer Science Course through NCCE
- 2020 Completed computer Science accelerator course through NCCE
- 2017 Learning to Teach: Mentoring and Tutoring Student Teachers (OU Course)

EMPLOYMENT EXPERIENCE

2023 – present North Kesteven Academy

Lincoln

- Planning and preparing resources
- Preparation of Classroom Materials for Media Lessons
- Running a coding club (Python/JavaScript)

Delivery of Computer Science and RE lessons

2017 – 2022 HUMBERSTON ACADEMY

Cleethorpes

- Teacher of Computer Science
- STEM Co-Ordinator for school events
- Preparation of Classroom Materials for GCSE Computer Science
- Running a coding club as an after-school activity/ delivering lessons

2014-2017 SKEGNESS ACADEMY

Skegness

Teacher of ICT and Computing

- Delivery of ICT and Computer Science to KS3, KS4 and KS5
- Role as a Year 9 Tutor (Previously Sixth form and Y10 Tutor)
- Teaching GCSE Computer Science Specification
- Preparation of Classroom Materials for Computing, Computer Science and ICT

2008-2014 **SUPPLY DESK**

Various

Supply Teacher

Various supply/cover duties within Lincolnshire (daily cover and long-term supply)

2006-2008 **HEALING SCHOOL**

Teacher of ICT

Grimsby

- Delivery of ICT lessons to KS3 and KS4 Students
- Class Tutor
- Preparing Schemes of Work

2001-2005 THE HUMBERSTON SCHOOL

Humberston

Teaching Assistant (ICT Specific)

- ICT Specific Teaching Assistant
- Responsible for supporting students and providing assistance ICT lessons

SKILLS

Have practical experience teaching python programming language for KS3 and KS4. I can use GitHub to
create repositories and use git bash command line to add and commit code to GitHub. I have created a
range of different resources using HTML, CSS and JavaScript.

EDUCATION AND TRAINING

March 2023	ED X BOOTCAMP	Remote Learning UK
	Front Find Dovision or Course	

Front End Developer Course

June 2006 Sheffield HALLAM UNIVERSITY Sheffield, UK

PGCE in ICT

June 2004 HULL UNIVERSITY Hull, UK

BA (Hons) Social and Behavioral Studies

February 2004 LINCOLN COLLEGE Lincoln, UK

BCS ECDL (Level 2) ECDL Advanced Database & Word Processing

Certificate in Adult literacy

June 2003 FRANKLIN COLLEGE Grimsby, UK

A level: ICT (Grade D)

June 2002 THE HUMBERSTON SCHOOL Cleethorpes, UK

GCSE ICT (Grade A) GCSE Mathematics (Grade B)

REFERENCES

Anthony Edmondson Work Reference Caistor Yarborough Academy Caistor LN7 6Qz

Tel: 07704694612

Ed X Boot Camp Academic Reference (Can Provide on Interview)